Guide to the New York City Taxi Drivers' Union, Local 3036 Audio Recordings OH.028
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
New York City Taxi Drivers' Union, Local 3036 Audio Recordings
1966-1981
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
OH.028
5 Linear Feet in 4 cassette boxes and 3 record cartons
133 audiocassettes
125 sound tape reels
The New York City Taxi Drivers' Union, Local 3036 Audio Recordings consist of 258 audio recordings of Union meetings, radio interviews, educational programs, and lectures dating from 1966 to 1981. The recordings portray the internal and external organizing activities of Union members as well as the organizational structure of the Union. The New York City Taxi Drivers' Union, Local 3036 was formed on July 1, 1966 and Harry Van Arsdale, Jr. was elected its first president. In the 1970s, Local 3036 became affiliated with the Service Employees International Union (SEIU).
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by New York City Taxi Drivers' Union, Local 3036 in 1985. The accession number associated with this gift is 1950.076.
Arrangement
This collection has been arranged into three Series:
Series I. Meeting Recordings, 1966-1981
Series II. Radio Shows, 1966-1976
Series III. Educational Programs and Lectures, 1967-1977
Historical Note
The New York City Taxi Drivers' Union, Local 3036 was formed on July 1, 1966 and elected Harry Van Arsdale, Jr., as their first President. At its peak, Local 3036 had almost 35,000 members. Local 3036 was active until the late 1980s, when it dissolved and merged with SEIU Local 74.
Van Arsdale also directed the establishment of the Union's predecessor, the Taxi Driver's Organizing Committee (TDOC). In the year leading up to the Local 3036's formation, the TDOC won elections conducted by the National Labor Relations in 82 garages throughout the city and came to represent nearly 18,000 taxi drivers and other workers within the fleet garages.
Source: Zeiger, Henry. "Hailing cab drivers: Labor's lost opportunity." September 21, 2023. https://laborers.tripod.com/AUD_120_p3.html.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact [Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596] with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Scope and Contents
The New York City Taxi Drivers' Union, Local 3036 Audio Recordings consist of 258 audio recordings which portray the internal and external organizing activities of Union members as well as the organizational structure of the Union. Meeting recordings (1966-1981) include Chair and Committee Meetings, Delegate Advisory Meetings, General Membership Meetings, Special Meetings, Strike Meetings, Charter Meetings, and Taxi Owner/Driver Division Meetings. Audio recordings of radio and television shows (1966-1976) document interviews and public appearances of Union members, as well as breaking news about the Union and the industry. Educational programs and lectures include class recordings, scholarship award ceremonies, foundation luncheons, and lectures and speeches given by Union members.
Related Materials
For information on the Taxi Rank and File Coalition (TRFC), an organized group of disenchanted members of the New York City Taxi Drivers Union, Local 3036, see The Taxi Rank and File Coalition Records (WAG.139).
Taxicab drivers -- New York (State) -- New York -- Interviews.; Taxicab drivers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York.; Labor unions -- Organizing -- New York (N.Y.); Audiocassettes.; Audiotapes.; Van Arsdale, Harry, 1905-1986; New York City Taxi Drivers Union, Local 3036; Taxi Drivers and Allied Workers Union. Local 3036, SEIU
- Series I. Meeting Recordings, 1966-1981; 114 audiocassettes; 55 sound tape reels
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged in chronological order.
  Scope and Contents
  Series I. Meeting Recordings (1966-1981) includes Chair and Committee Meetings, Delegate Advisory Meetings, General Membership Meetings, Special Meetings, Strike Meetings, Charter Meetings, and Taxi Owner/Driver Division Meetings.
  - Charter Meeting, Van Arsdale on Vacation Time, August 14, 1966 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0134)
  - Meeting on Vacation Grievances, Prince George Hotel, August 22, 1966 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0135, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0136, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0137)
  - Constitution and By-Law Meeting, Manhattan Center, September 13, 1966 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0138)
  - Over 60 Year Olds Meeting, Prince George Hotel, September 13, 1966 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0139)
  - Taxi Pension Meeting, Prince George Hotel, September 13, 1966 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0140)
  - Special Committee Meeting, Prince George Hotel, September 14, 1966 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0141)
  - Taxi Owner-Driver Division Meeting, Prince George Hotel, September 28, 1966 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0142)
  - Taxi Owner-Driver Division Meeting, January 20, 1967 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0143)
  - Taxi Drivers Meeting, Manhattan Center, April 12, 1967 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0144, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0145)
  - Chair Reports, October 11, 1967 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0146)
  - Delegates Advisory Council, Prince George Hotel, November 23, 1967 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0147)
  - Chair Meeting, Prince George Hotel, January 5, 1968 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0148)
  - Copper Strike Meeting, Commodore Hotel, February 10, 1968 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0149)
  - Harry Van Arsdale and Mike Mann, Manhattan Center, March 17, 1968 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0150)
  - General Membership Meeting, Manhattan Center, April 10, 1968 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0151, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0152, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0153)
  - Taxi Owner-Driver Division Meeting, Prince George Hotel, April 23, 1968 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0154)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, Prince George Hotel, October 3, 1968 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0155, Box Shared Tamiment 157, Folder 19)
    Includes paper notes from meeting.
  - General Membership Meeting, Manhattan Center, October 9, 1968 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0156, Box Shared Tamiment 157, Folder 20)
  - Special Membership Meeting, Manhattan Center, February 1, 1969 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0157)
  - Advisory Council Meeting, Prince George Hotel, June 9, 1969 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0158, Box Shared Tamiment 157, Folder 21)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, Prince George Hotel, July 21, 1969 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0159, Box Shared Tamiment 157, Folder 22)
  - Advisory Council and Chair Meeting, September 20, 1969 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0043)
  - General Membership Meeting, Manhattan Center, October 8, 1969 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0160, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0161)
  - Police Award Ceremony, Police Academy, November 20, 1969 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0162)
  - Taxi Owner-Driver Division Committee Meeting, Prince George Hotel, February 10, 1970 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0163)
  - Taxi Owner-Driver Division Meeting, February 15, 1970 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0164)
  - Advisory Council and Chair Meeting, Prince George Hotel, March 10, 1970 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0044)
  - Chair Meeting, Prince George Hotel, March 10, 1970 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0165)
  - Chair Meeting, April 3, 1970 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0131)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, Prince George Hotel, April 3, 1970; cuid907 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0001)
  - General Membership Meeting, Manhattan Center, April 8, 1970 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0166, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0167)
  - Special Meeting, Union Headquarters, July 10, 1970 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0045)
  - "Inside Men" Meeting, Penn Gardens Hotel, July 29, 1970 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0168)
  - General Membership Meeting, Manhattan Center, October 14, 1970 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0169)
  - Shop Chair "Strike" Meeting, Manhattan Center, December, 1970 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0170)
  - Special Strike Meeting, Manhattan Center, December 4, 1970 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0171)
  - Taxi Owner-Driver Division Meeting, Commodore Hotel, October 14, 1970 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0046)
  - Chair Meeting, Commodore Hotel, October 16, 1970 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0047)
    Includes address by Governor Rockefeller
  - Meeting, November 11, 1970 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0048)
  - Delegate Body Meeting, Chair and Committee Meeting, Commodore Hotel, November 16, 1970; cuid908 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0002, 028_0003)
    Harry van Arsdale
  - Meeting on Negotiations, Advisory and Delegate Body, Commodore Hotel; Chairmen on Contract Negotiations Meeting, Union Office, November 19-20, 1970; cuid909 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0004)
  - Chair Meeting, November 28, 1970 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0049, Audiocassette 028_0050)
    Includes contract negation, Van Arsdale, housing and agreement
  - Contract and Pension Meeting, Manhattan Center, December 20, 1970 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0051)
    Includes ratification of contract
  - Signing of Taxi Commission Bill, City Hall, March 1, 1971 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0052)
  - Chair Meeting, Prince George Hotel, March 30, 1971 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0053)
  - General Membership Meeting, Manhattan Center, April 14, 1971 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0174)
  - Chair Committee Meeting, Brooklyn, April 24, 1971; cuid910 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0005)
  - Contract and Pension Meeting and Luncheon, Commodore Hotel, May 5, 1971 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0054)
  - Contract and Pension Meeting, Helen Garage, May 10, 1971 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0055)
    Includes officers' report on contract negotiations, discussion between councilmen, and speech by unidentified speaker
  - Contract and Pension Meeting, Commodore Hotel, June 24, 1971 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0056)
    Regarding contract negotiations
  - Chair Committee Meeting, Commodore Hotel, June 26, 1971; cuid911 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0006)
  - Chair Committee Meeting, Prince George Hotel, July 15, 1971; cuid912 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0007, 028_0008)
  - Taxi Owner-Driver Division Meeting, Prince George Hotel, August 10, 1971 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0057)
  - General Membership Meeting, Manhattan Center, October 13, 1971 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0175)
  - Shop Chair Meeting, October 24, 1971 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0058)
  - Special Meeting, City Hall, circa 1971 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0172, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0173)
    Harry Van Arsdale speaks at City Hall, requesting redress of inequities in pay to taxi drivers, and rising sentiment of union for a strike. Warns that action to take place in coming days is only a protest demonstration to the City Council, not a strike."
  - Chair Meeting, Union Headquarters, January 30, 1972 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0059)
  - Chair Meeting, Union Headquarters, February 6, 1972 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0060, Audiocassette 028_0061)
  - Chair Meeting, Union Headquarters, February 20, 1972 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0062)
  - Chair Meeting, February 27, 1972 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0063, Audiocassette 028_0064)
  - Chair Meeting, March 5, 1972 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0065)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, Prince George Hotel, April 10, 1972; cuid913 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0009)
  - Taxi Owner-Driver Division Meeting, June 6, 1972 (Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0176)
  - Shop Chair and Committee Meeting, at Local 1199, August 21, 1972 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0010, 028_0011)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, at Local 1199, October 9, 1972 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0012)
  - General Membership Meeting, Manhattan Center, October 11, 1972 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0066, Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0177)
  - "Inside Men" Meeting, November 13, 1972 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0121)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, at Local 1199, April 2, 1973 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0013)
  - General Membership Meeting, Manhattan Center, April 11, 1973 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0067, Box 5, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0178)
  - Shop Chair and Committee Meeting, at Local 1199, May 14, 1973 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0014)
  - Taxi Owner-Driver Division Meeting, May 23, 1973 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0179)
  - Taxi Owner-Driver Division Meeting, Manhattan Center, June 6, 1973 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0068)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, Union Headquarters, June 19, 1973 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0015)
  - Chair Meeting, Union Headquarters, September 12, 1973 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0069)
  - General Membership Meeting, Manhattan Center, October 10, 1973 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0070, Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0180)
  - Chair and Committee Special Meeting, Prince George Hotel, November 24, 1973 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0018)
  - General Meeting, Manhattan Center, April 10, 1974 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0071, Audiocassette 028_0072)
  - Shop Chair and Committee Meeting, Prince George Hotel, August 5, 1974 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0016)
  - Shop Chair and Committee Special Meeting, Prince George Hotel, August 9, 1974 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0017)
  - Contract and Pension Meeting, Manhattan Center, September 4, 1974 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0073, Audiocassette 028_0074)
  - Swearing in of Officers with the American Arbitration Association, November 11-12, 1974 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0075, Audiocassette 028_0076, Audiocassette 028_0077)
  - Taxi Owner-Driver Division Meeting, Travelers Hotel, December 22, 1974 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0078, Audiocassette 028_0079, Audiocassette 028_0080)
  - Shop Chair Meeting, Bakery Union Long Island City, December 30, 1974 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0081)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, at Local 199, March 18, 1975 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0019)
  - Contract and Pension Meeting, March 18, 1975 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0082)
  - Contract and Pension Meeting, Prince George Hotel, March 19, 1975 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0083)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, Union Headquarters, April 27, 1976 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0021, 028_0022)
  - Shop Chair Meeting, Union Headquarters, June 23, 1975 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0084)
  - General Membership Meeting, Manhattan Center, October 8, 1975 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0085)
  - Shop Chair Meeting, October 23, 1975 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0086)
  - Shop Chair and Committee Meeting, Union Headquarters, December 30, 1975 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0020)
  - Shop Chair Meeting, Union Headquarters, February 24, 1976 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0087)
  - Meeting at Police Headquarters, March, 1976 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0088)
    Regarding the Rodriguez murder
  - Taxi Owner-Driver Division Meeting, March 19, 1976 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0089)
  - General Membership Meeting, Manhattan Center, May 12, 1976 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0090, Audiocassette 028_0091)
  - Contract and Pension Meeting, June 21, 1976 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0092)
    Includes address by Greenblatt regarding the Employee Retirement Income Security Act (ERISA)
  - Chair Meeting, Union Headquarters, June 29, 1976 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0093)
  - Contract and Pension Meeting, Hotel Plaza, July 19, 1976 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0094)
    Regarding rules and regulations of ERISA
  - Delegate Advisory Meeting, August 23, 1976 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0023)
  - Application Hearing for Long Island Taxi Association, September 2, 1976 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0095, Audiocassette 028_0096)
  - General Membership Meeting, Statler Hilton Hotel, October 13, 1976 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0097, Audiocassette 028_0098)
  - Chair Meeting, October 25, 1976 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0099)
  - Contract and Pension Meeting, October 28, 1976 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0100)
    Regarding contract, leasing, strikes
  - Special Meeting, Statler Hilton Hotel, November 18, 1976 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0101, Audiocassette 028_0102)
  - Contract and Pension Meeting, 1976 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0103)
  - Chair Meeting, January 12, 1977 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0104)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, Union Office, April 11, 1977 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0024)
  - General Membership Meeting, April 13, 1977 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0105)
  - Chair Meeting, August 22, 1977 (Box 3, Audiocassette 028_0106)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, October 11, 1977 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0025)
  - General Membership Meeting, October 12, 1977 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0107)
  - Chair Meeting, November 18, 1977 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0108)
  - General Membership Meeting, April 12, 1978 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0109)
  - Chair Meeting, May 4, 1978 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0110)
  - Chair Meeting, June 2, 1978 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0111)
  - Chair Meeting, July 13, 1978 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0112)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, September 21, 1978 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0026)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, October 18, 1978 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0027)
  - Meeting with Newark Airport Taxi Workers, November 13, 1978 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0113)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, November 27, 1978 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0028)
  - General Membership Meeting, April 25, 1979 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0114)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, July 12, 1979 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0029)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, August 8, 1979 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0030)
  - Chair Meeting, Union Headquarters, September 24, 1979 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0115)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, November 2, 1979 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0031)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, November 8, 1979 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0032)
  - Contract and Pension Meeting, January 21, 1980 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0116)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, June 11, 1980 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0033)
  - Contract and Pension Meeting, July 2, 1980 (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0117)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, June 29, 1981 (Box 1, Audiocassette 028_0034)
  - Advisory Board Meeting, Commodore Hotel, Undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0132)
    Regarding negotiations
  - Advisory Council and Delegates Body Meeting, Prince George Hotel, Undated (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0181)
  - Chair and Committee Meeting, Undated (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0182)
    Includes Harry Van Arsdale and Tom Iandoli
  - Chair Meeting, Undated (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0183)
  - Chair Meeting, Mozart Hall, Undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0133)
  - Contract and Pension Meeting, Undated (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0184)
    Includes a pension report from Bill Deegan
  - Delegates Body Meeting, Hotel Penn Gardens, Undated (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0185)
  - General Membership Meeting, Roosevelt Auditorium, Undated (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0186)
  - Special Meeting, Undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0120)
    Hearings on drivers going to Black neighborhoods
  - Taxi Owner-Driver Division, Undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0119)
  - Taxi Owner-Driver Division Interviews, Undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 028_0118)
    Regarding Yellow Cab Law
  - Taxi Owner-Driver Division Meeting, Maritime Hall, Undated (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0187)
    With Van Arsdale and Chaloupka
  - Taxi Owner-Driver Division Meeting, Webster Hall, Undated (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0188)
  - Union Meeting, Undated (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0189)
    Includes an address by Mr. Dejahns
  - Wagner Meeting, George Washington Hotel, Undated (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0190)
- Series II. Radio Shows, 1966-1976; 10 audiocassettes; 59 sound tape reels
  Series II. Radio Shows includes audio recordings of radio and television shows (1966-1976), which include interviews and public appearances of Union members, as well as breaking news about the Union and the industry.
  - "Talk of New York," WCBS, April 1, 1966 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0191)
    With Peter Brennan
  - Taxi Hearings, WNYC, August 31, 1966 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0192, 028_0193)
  - "Protection for Cab Drivers," Victor Riesel Show, WOR, September 25, 1966 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0194)
  - "State of the Unions," WCBS-TV, November 15, 1966 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0195)
  - "Critics Circle," WOR, November 22, 1966 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0196)
  - Taxi Driver Awards, WNEW, December 1, 1966 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0197)
    With Steve Bell at 5pm and Paul Lockwood at 11pm
  - "Taxi Cab Crises," Joe Franklin Show, WOR, December 8, 1966 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0198)
  - "Taxicabs," Barry Gray Show, WMCA, January 8, 1967 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0199)
  - "Arthur Turkisher, MTBT, Abraham Dellis, Cabbie," Jack O'Brian Show, WOR, January 30, 1967 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0200, 028_0201)
  - Barry Gray Show, WMCA, May 14, 1967 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0202)
  - "Governor Hughes, Migrant Farm Workers," WINS, July 21, 1967 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0203)
  - "Taxicab Drivers," Barry Farber Show, WOR, October 4, 1967 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0204, 028_0205, 028_0206, 028_0207, 028_0208)
  - Barry Gray Show, WMCA, October 15, 1967 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0209)
  - Barry Gray Show, WMCA, November 21, 1967 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0220)
    Includes interviews with Harry Van Arsdale and Tom Iandoli
  - "At Noon," WOR, December 29, 1967 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0221)
    Includes interviews with Arthur Turkisher and Tom Iandoli
  - "Taxicabs," Barry Gray Show, WMCA, January 4, 1968 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0210)
  - "Taxicab Hearings," WNYC, January 8, 1968 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0211, 028_0212, 028_0213, 028_0214, 028_0215, 028_0216)
  - "Taxicabs," Alan Burke Show, WNEW-TV, January 11, 1968 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0217)
  - "Taxicabs," Sixth Hour News, WNBC-TV, January 19, 1968 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0218)
  - Harry Van Arsdale on "Searchlight," WNBC-TV, February 11, 1968 (Box 6, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0219)
  - Interview of Cab Drivers and Report on Gypsy Driver, WINS, March 16, 1968 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0222)
  - "Gypsy Taxis," Newsprint, WNDT TV NY, July 9, 1968 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0223)
  - "Gypsy Cabs," Equal Time, WPIX-TV, July 13, 1968 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0224)
  - "Phil Rosemblum, MTBT, Cal Williams, Direct Line," WNBC-TV, July 14, 1968 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0225)
  - "Badillo's Slur on HVA," Searchlight, WNBC-TV, April 20, 1969 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0226)
  - News, WINS, April 23, 1969 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0227)
  - "Taxi Cab Mess," The Long John Nebel Show, WNBC, August 5, 1969 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0228)
  - "Taxi," Barry Gray Show, WOR-TV, December 9, 1969 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0229)
  - "Taxicabs," New York Illustrated, WNBC-TV, January 3, 1970 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0230)
  - Godfrey Cambridge on The Marv Griffin Show, CBS, January 12, 1970 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0231)
  - Taxi Editorial, WINS, January 23, 1970 (Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0232)
  - "Report on the Death of a Cab Driver," WNEW-TV, February 13, 1970 (Box 2, Audiocassette 028_0035, Box 7, Quarter inch audio reel 028_0233)